

niels.henning@xs4all.nl

(06) 81 29 48 35

(nielshenning.eu)

Alphen aan den Rijn



EDUCATION

GRAFISCH LYCEUM UTRECHT

Third Year

2020 - Present

GROENE HART LEERPARK VMBO-KADER (MEDIA)

2016 - 2020

NIELS HENNING

GAME DEVELOPER

PROFILE

I am an 18-year-old boy who lives in the Netherlands and loves to play games. I started the game development course because I was interested how the back of the game looked and what's happening in the background of the game to go from hobby to work.

LANGUAGE

Dutch = 9/10English = 7/10

EXPERIENCE

PICNIC - DELIVERY

(Current job)

Delivering groceries and having conversations with clients

JUMBO - CASHIER

(19-08-2021 - 12-06-2022)

I've been working as a consistent cashier at the jumbo for almost a year and a half now. So, I have a lot of experience talking to people

JUMBO - FILLING CREW EMPLOYEE

(7-11-2019 - 19-08-2021)

I started working at the jumbo as filling crew employee since I was 15 years old and when I turned 16, I started working as a cashier.

SKILLS

- C#
- C++
- HTML
- CSS
- Animations
- Cutscenes
- Unity
- GitHub

